Ilya Rozanov?
Shane Hollander.
I--I wanted to introduce myself.
Oh, I'm--I'm not sure
you're supposed to smoke here.
OK.
You're an awesome
player to watch.
Yes.
Anyways, I--I should go.
They're waiting for me.
But, um, good luck
in the tournament.
You will not be so nice
when we beat you.
That's not happening.
See you in final.
It may be cold
in Saskatchewan,
but here at the
International Prospect Cup,
fans are hoping
for something hot on the ice,
a Canada-Russia final
showcasing the two most talked
about prospects in the world:
Canada's Shane Hollander
and Russia's Ilya Rozanov.
First, you've got Ottawa's
own Shane Hollander.
From everything
we've seen and heard,
he may not be the most sociable,
but this is the kid with
the highest hockey IQ out there.
Incredibly smart,
incredibly dedicated to the game
and incredibly fast.
And that shot!
Then you've got
Russia's Ilya Rozanov.
Strong on the puck
and a strong skater.
And from everything
we've heard,
he really gets under
other players' skins.
Good in his own room,
not exactly liked
in his opponent's room.
- My kind of player.
- Boston's kind of player too.
Rozanov! Is there something
more important going on?
A heartbreaking loss
for a young Canadian team
still searching for an identity
despite an incredible showing
from the teenage phenom
Shane Hollander.
He just couldn't get past
that elite Russian defense.
And more importantly,
Ilya Rozanov
kept getting past theirs.
See you at the draft.
All right, boys,
looking over here.
Flash me those numbers.
Ha! Number three's excited.
There's one.
Where's number two?
There we go.
Can I get a smile please?
Yeah, that's better!
All right.
I can't tell you how excited
Montrealers are about this.
We don't care
he came number two.
People are popping champagne
all over Quebec.
Oh, and, uh,
just to be clear,
uh, we are thrilled that Shane
is Asian, or Asian-Canadian.
Very thrilled.
I mean, we've historically
broken barriers,
and we're doing it again,
so nothing to worry about there.
Oh. You certainly have.
And, I mean, to be a part of
the most legendary franchise
in hockey, right?
Oh, my!
It's, uh...
I'm still in shock,
but, uh, I--I'm so excited.
And I know this came up
in Shane's interview,
but I am the world's
biggest Metros fan.
Really?
It's part of how
I came to feel Canadian.
My dad would sit us down in
the living room Saturday nights.
We're not passing on a kid
this strong with those hands,
not in Boston, Mr. Rozanov.
He's a very natural
number one pick.
Congratulations again, Ilya.
He is strong,
but he needs discipline.
He can be, how you say, lazy.
I find that hard to believe,
the way he plays!
I promise to work
very hard for you.
I have no doubt you will, son.
You listen. Don't speak.
You understand?
Yes.
Ah!
Whoo!
What a fucking day, huh?
Yeah, totally.
Mmm.
It's everything you dreamed of?
Almost.
I'm sorry.
No, you're not.
Montreal is...
It's nice, yes?
Yeah, it's awesome.
Boston is nice too?
I think so.
People like it there.
We will, uh... we will be
seeing each other a lot.
Yeah, Boston and Montreal
play against each other often.
More...
Hmm.
THE COLONEL
What the fuck is going on?
Why is Dad calling me?
Baby brother,
happy New Year for you, right?
Happy New Year, Alexei, but.
How's it going, handsome boy?
What is going on with Dad?
What the fuck are you
talking about? Dad is fine.
He keeps calling me.
'Cause you lost
a fucking hockey game, idiot.
What the fuck
do you want from me, Alexei?
Let me think about it!
Can I have more money?
Please.
I have no more money, Alexei!
My bonus is done, man.
You snorted most of it!
Wah-wah, you whiny faggot.
Go fuck yourself.
Go fuck yourself, bitch.
Hello, Father.
And so he answers!
I'm sorry, Father.
Apologize to Russia.
Losing to the Czechs.
Disgusting.
We will beat Sweden, Father.
Beat Sweden?
You will have to!
Otherwise, you will.
Not play for good.
I know, Father.
We are all trying.
I don't care about "we"!
You! You will not lose to him.
What a comeback for Canada!
A huge win for
the hometown boys tonight,
who were determined to not
lose to Russia on home ice
two years in a row.
Good game. Good game.
See you in October.
That looks good.
Camera, you're happy with that?
All right, that's perfect.
Give us a second.
We'll be good to go, OK?
Just stay there.
Hold, please. Thank you.
You look pretty.
You're wearing makeup too.
Yeah, but I don't look pretty.
Great. Can we do it again?
Can you guys try to hit
those marks at the same time?
Just skate out and skate in with
a lot of intensity, all right?
- OK.
- Action!
Good. OK, let's do that
one more time.
Great. OK, one more time.
Great. OK!
Guys, just hold there
for a second.
We're gonna make a little tweak
here with the camera.
I'll let you know when
we're ready to go.
In 3, 2, 1, and go ahead.
OK. I get it, guys.
It's been a long day. I know.
- Sorry.
Try with a lot
of intensity, though.
OK?
- OK.
OK. One more time, guys.
The more serious we can do,
the quicker we go home. Go.
I'm sorry.
OK.
Oh, I can do it. I promise.
And three, two, one, go ahead.
OK.
OK, I think we have what
we are gonna get here.
Thanks, guys!
When they tell you
you do commercial with me
and not just alone?
I don't know,
like, two days ago?
Why? When did they tell you?
No, they told me nothing.
It was my idea.
Shane!
Shane, are you
listening to me?
What? Yeah.
OK, so what did I just say?
Sneakers, I heard.
OK, you have to be seen
in your Reeboks.
I know, Mom.
Because you cannot
be in anything else.
Mom, I'm always
wearing skates.
But in case you're not.
This is a lot of money, Shane.
You're the youngest
hockey player
they've ever signed to a deal.
And remember
what else this means.
I remember.
A whole lot of kids are
gonna be looking up to you,
kids that don't
see themselves here a lot.
I get it, Mom.
Fuck off.
Not here.
So, uh, look, we can forget
that happened in there, OK?
Is what you want?
Yeah, for sure.
Oh, wow.
You are a really bad liar.
What is your room number?
1410.
Well, if I come
to 1410 tonight at 9:00...
I might open.
I might knock.
♪ She drink coffee, sea lion ♪
♪ She drink tea, sea lion ♪
♪ And rooster crows, sea lion ♪
♪ Sea lion woman ♪
♪ Dressed in white ♪
♪ Marry the man ♪
♪ And you'll spend
a long, sweet life ♪
What are you doing, dude?
♪ Dressed in green ♪
♪ Silver lining
and golden seams ♪
♪ Sea lion woman ♪
♪ Dressed in blue ♪
♪ Call on man and hope
he knows what he can do ♪
No, stop it.
Just stop it.
♪ Sea lion, sea lion,
sea lion... ♪
Oh, hello there.
Oh, I'm trying to go down.
This is going up.
- Right.
- So...
Yeah, OK.
Well, I'm... Ah!
Oh, ah!
♪ Sea lion woman,
sea lion woman ♪
♪ Sea lion woman... ♪
I thought you might chicken out.
I'm not. I'm not a chicken.
But I think we should talk.
Do you want to sit?
Mmm, not really.
This is such a bad idea.
What is?
Fuck, Hollander.
Oh, stop, stop, stop.
Was that bad?
Ah, no, opposite.
Is too much, too good.
Is your first time with a man?
You?
No.
Really?
Really.
Who? Another player?
No, my coach's son
back in Russia.
I like trouble.
Weren't you scared
of getting caught?
No.
It was nothing serious,
and we had the same secret,
so it was just...
Curious?
Curious.
And you make me curious.
Do I make you curious?
Obviously.
Did you like sucking my cock?
Wow. Those English words
just roll off your tongue.
Yes?
Yes.
You want me to, uh,
lie on the bed
and let you do it some more?
- Let me?
- Yeah.
Uh, not fair.
Come on, I want to see you.
You saw me in the showers.
Yeah, I want more.
OK.
Come here.
So what do you want to do?
I don't know.
Is this OK?
Da, like that, Hollander.
Fuck, Hollander.
Ah, fuck. Oh.
Not bad for first time.
Fuck you, Rozanov.
OK. It was fun.
Are you serious?
What?
What? You need something?
You think I am asshole?
I know you're an asshole.
Oh. I would not
leave you like that.
No?
No.
Let me show you
how to do this, kid.
Holy shit, Rozanov.
Oh, fuck.
Holy shit, Rozanov,
you better get off.
I'm... I can't stop.
Oh, fuck!
Rozanov, fuck, fuck, fuck.
Oh my God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh my God. I'm so sorry.
I--I didn't think.
What? That you would
come so quick?
Fuck you.
You didn't have to.
I don't mind.
This is, uh...
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
God, I want a cigarette.
Smoking is bad for you.
Oh, is it?
So...
you're not gonna tell
anyone about this, are you?
Me?
Yes, Hollander,
I'm going to tell everyone.
'Cause no one can know.
Hollander, look,
I'm not going to tell anyone.
OK?
- OK.
I, uh, I have early
flight tomorrow, so...
Yeah, me too.
Good night.
Night.
Holy shit!
How are you feeling
about finally getting
to Montreal tomorrow?
Good. About time.
Are you looking forward to
beating Shane Hollander?
Uh, he is goalie now, yes?
Ilya, at the beginning
of the year,
you said you would score
40 goals your rookie season.
You still feel
that's going to happen?
No, no. I never said 40 goals.
It's a lie. Liar told you that.
I said 50.
What a fucking asshole.
Ah!
Sorry I'm late.
It's 15 minutes.
Don't even worry about it.
We don't care. It's just that
you're usually on time.
My workout went
longer than expected,
and I got lost
in a YouTube rabbit hole.
It's fine. I ordered for you.
Salmon, brown rice.
- Thanks.
- OK.
So, I have very exciting news.
What's YouTube?
Rolex is in.
Wow!
Let me pull up the email.
And I quote...
"Shane is exactly the kind
of young athlete and young man
"that Rolex wants to
be associated with.
He's smart, he's serious,
he's handsome."
That's an understatement.
- God, Mom.
"And we believe he will be
hockey's most significant
ambassador in a generation."
Is Rolex on YouTube?
YouTube is like
a video portal site.
I'm not convinced I know
what any of those words mean.
So, a rabbit hole
is where you watch a video,
it recommends other videos,
and you keep clicking them.
Sounds dangerous.
Oh, yeah.
I go down those rabbit
holes all the time.
Of course you do, Mom.
- What was yours about?
- Fancy watches?
- David!
- What? I'm just keeping up.
Unlikely animals
becoming friends,
like a tiger and a bear,
a cow and a duck.
Come on!
Yeah, a snake and a baby.
I'd watch that.
Well, what you
should be watching
are the ones about hockey.
I think keeping up
with that snake and baby
sounds pretty important.
Relationship could go sideways
pretty fast.
Oh, I saw a link today
about Ilya Rozanov.
So I click on it, and he says...
Well, first of all,
do you remember at
the beginning of the season,
he told someone,
I can't remember who...
Anyway, he told them that
he was gonna score 40 goals.
Do you remember that?
I remember you
yelling something
about Rozanov turning 40
and me trying to match
your level of outrage.
Well, yesterday in Boston,
he said he meant 50.
50 goals!
Yeah, he's an asshole.
Yeah, the nerve. Fuck him!
I'm sorry, but I mean it.
OK, imagining he's better
than Gretzky? Better than you?
Fuck him. Right up the butt.
Yuna!
I'm sorry, but I said it.
Honestly!
Desjardins talking to
McCann and St. Pierre.
It's probably the last
face-off of the game.
Who are they sending in?
The crowd seems to have ideas.
Are they gonna do this?
Are they gonna give the people
what they want?
Desjardins is gonna
give it to them.
Is Reilly gonna do this too?
Are we gonna see...
Listen to that crowd.
And there you have it!
It's Ilya Rozanov versus...
Shane Hollander.
Will you disappoint them?
No.
But a goal off the face-off?
Your first against Rozanov?
That had to have
felt pretty good?
I'm happy with
any goal I can get.
But one off of Rozanov?
Again, I'm happy
with any goal.
And the face-offs?
I'm here for the team.
I'm here to win.
I don't care about the details.
And what do you think
about being compared
to Tiger Woods
and Serena Williams?
Do you think you share
any of the same challenges?
I don't really think
about stuff like that.
I'm just super happy
to play for the Metros.
Mr. Hollander...
How does it feel to be perfect?
Fucking perfect.
Thanks for asking.
In fucking French.
Twenty thousand dollars?
Yes, twenty thousand dollars.
I'm glad your hearing is OK.
For what this time?
For fuck you.
This is the last fucking time.
Yeah, fine.
And I'm not
sending it tonight!
Why the fuck not?
It's. It's midnight here,
Alexei.
You always have
some bullshit excuse, Ilya.
How's Dad?
What the fuck is up
with you and Dad?
Jesus fucking Christ!
He is fine!
We can all live without you.
Go fuck yourself, Ilya.
On the phone yesterday,
he asked me
to bring home some bread.
Well, he is stupid!
Good night, Alexei.
First thing
in the morning, Ilya.
Here we are
at the MLH All-Star Game,
and the theme this year
is Team Hollander
versus Team Rozanov.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I read that wrong.
It's Team North America
versus Team Europe.
It's not subtle.
Anytime the league
can figure out a way
to get these two kids
in each other's faces,
they're gonna do it.
Ilya, you're having
a legendary rookie season.
Both of you are.
You said you'd hit
50 goals this year.
You've had 28 so far, and we're
in the middle of February.
You still thinking
about a 50-goal campaign?
Yes.
Shane, kind of
the same to you.
You scored 31 goals.
Any chance you want to speculate
as to how this season
will end up for you guys?
No chance at all.
Question for Ilya first,
but it'll be the same for Shane.
Boston is an original six
legendary team
that's struggled
to get to the playoffs
for the past 3 seasons.
How much pressure do you feel
from the fans,
from the hockey world
in general,
to restore Boston
to its former glory?
And how much of that do
you take on personally?
Um...
Uh...
Sorry, not to
jump the gun here,
but with Rozanov's permission...
I know it's only been
two seasons
since Montreal's
made the playoffs,
but I think I get the idea.
So, look, my mom is
the world's biggest Metros fan.
She's obsessed.
And like all Metros fans,
she wants us to be back
in the playoffs regularly,
and she wants us
to win some cups.
And I want the same thing.
I want to be in the playoffs,
and I want to win some cups.
I feel pretty aligned
with the fans,
'cause we want the same thing.
And at this point, it's my job
to take that personally.
Ilya?
What he said.
And here's the
shot accuracy competition,
featuring, gasp, Shane Hollander
and Ilya Rozanov.
The record for this event,
currently held by the
New York Admiral's Scott Hunter,
is 4 takedowns in 8 seconds.
Come on!
And Rozanov breaks the record.
There you go!
He's a big kid
with a big shot.
That was something else,
I'll tell you that!
Let's go!
Shane Hollander just shaved
over a second
off the record
that Ilya Rozanov just set.
If that isn't a good night
and good luck,
I don't know what is.
Good job.
Thanks.
You have fun last night?
Last night?
With your team.
Get dinner, get drunk?
Oh, yeah. I mean, I had fun,
but I didn't get drunk.
You?
Yeah, it was great.
No boring Canadians,
no stupid Americans.
So, what, just a bunch
of Finnish guys
talking about the cousins
they're in love with?
Think I'm going to bed
early tonight.
Oh, yeah?
1221.
Nice shooting, rook.
Thanks.
Glad to see Rozanov
didn't hold my record
for more than a minute.
What did he want, by the way?
Oh, nothing,
just shit-talking.
He's an asshole, right?
I mean, yeah, basically.
Lucky me.
I'm in the room next door
to him at the hotel.
Hollander!
Is someone chasing you?
I'm standing in the hallway
like an idiot.
Scott Hunter is right next door.
Fuck.
Get on your knees.
Oh my fucking...
Fuck, Rozanov.
Get on your stomach.
On your stomach.
Have you ever?
Do you want to?
You're scared.
I'm not scared.
No, it's OK.
Do you ever
touch yourself here?
Jesus Christ.
What? Does touching your ass
make you gay?
Rozanov...
'Cause you know what else
makes you gay
is sucking my dick.
Shut up.
Fuck.
I'm trying to say
I have a thing. OK?
A thing?
A dildo.
What color?
Fuck you.
It's big?
I'm leaving.
No, no, Hollander.
I want to fuck you.
Not here.
Not with fucking
Scott Hunter next door.
He is hot.
We should let him listen
like mating call.
- You'd like that, wouldn't you?
- Mm-hmm.
You probably would too.
OK. So next time.
Next time?
Yeah, we're playing
Montreal in two weeks.
Yeah. But, um,
where would we...
Where would we what?
Meet?
You are homeless?
No.
Then we meet at your house.
It's an apartment.
Hollander, you are having
a panic attack.
It's just a plan to fuck.
Uh, I know we talked about
Montreal in two weeks, but...
Oh my God, Hollander,
you are so boring.
Give me your phone.
You have phone.
Give.
So, what's my name gonna be?
Jane.
What's up with you?
Nothing.
You sure?
Fuck you.
Hey, sorry, boys.
No one's getting
into Montreal today.
Two feet of snow.
Fuck. Fuck!
It's a night off, boy.
It's not the end of the world.
Yeah, whatever.
Look, whoever she is,
she's gonna get over it.
Hey, you, uh, you don't want
to come over to my place
for dinner tonight, do you?
What?
Since there's no game.
Come for dinner.
Jacki said it's cool.
Oh, that's my wife.
She can throw on some steaks.
I--I'm on a macrobiotic diet.
Buddy, I don't even know
what that means.
But Jacki can cook anything.
You OK?
- Yeah, I guess.
Hey, if you have other plans,
that's--that's totally cool.
No, I want to watch you eat
my disgusting food. Let's do it.
Fuck yes!
God, Jacki's gonna be so happy.
She's obsessed with being
the first wag to feed you.
I'm gonna text her
right now, actually.
"Bird food only."
Jesus Christ.
- Surprise!
- Svetlana!
I thought you were
back in Russia!
What the fuck
are you doing here?
Being nice,
but I already regret it.
Sounds like you.
Go fuck yourself, Ilya.
Sorry. I didn't expect you.
- How did you know.
- That your game was cancelled?
It was announced, asshole.
You don't deserve me.
I should go.
OK, now I'm really leaving,
you piece of shit.
Have fun with. Jane.
And the nominees
for Rookie of the Year are...
Shane Hollander,
the Montreal Metros,
Vincent Lemaire,
the Minnesota Nomads,
and Ilya Rozanov,
the Boston Raiders.
And the Rookie of the Year is...
Rook! Rook! Rook!
That better just be
ginger ale, rook.
It is, Mr. Hunter. I wouldn't
indulge in front of you.
- Congrats, man.
- Thank you.
Uh, what would you say if, uh,
me and some of
the other old fucks
wanted to do some shots
with the three rooks?
Would you be into that?
Fuck yes, I would.
OK. Then where's
your boy Rozanov?
My what?
No, I mean, not your boy.
Just, like, it's always, uh,
Hollander and Rozanov, right?
I just thought...
I don't know where he is.
We're not, like,
friends or anything.
No worries, man.
No worries. I'm sure someone
else grabbed him.
OK!
- Fuck yes!
- Ah!
- OK, one more!
♪ Two leaves in the air ♪
♪ Clean air in a room ♪
♪ That could go for 180 amount ♪
♪ Sat still inside by myself
with the lights turned off ♪
♪ The blinds all turned ♪
♪ No feedback ♪
I don't know if
it's worth jumping over.
Party all done?
No, I just need some air.
You are drunk.
I'm not.
Good for you.
Big night for you.
Yeah, well, it could have
gone to either one of us.
It went to you.
So what?
You're just up here sulking
because, what,
you couldn't take
another victory lap around me?
All you do is beat me.
I win one fucking thing, and
you can't even show your face.
What was that?
- Not everything is about you!
So what is it then?
What the fuck do you want?
Nothing. I just wanted to
see the view and get some air.
And what? Here is
fucking view, Hollander.
Check it out. Fuck!
I go home in three days.
OK.
That must be nice.
And I guess
I thought maybe we...
Never mind.
OK, I'm gonna...
I guess I'll, uh,
see you next season.
What the fuck are you doing?
We're both in tuxedos
out in public.
No one is looking.
You don't know that.
See you next season!
Hollander.
Closed Captions: MELS
www.tvsubtitles.net